{

	"quizId":1,
	"quizTypeId":1,
	"quizItems":[
		{

		"quizItemId":0,
		"quizId":1,
		"question":"5276d37b82",
		"answer":"5276d37b82"
		
},
		{

		"quizItemId":1,
		"quizId":1,
		"question":"a421821896",
		"answer":"a421821896"
		
},
		{

		"quizItemId":2,
		"quizId":1,
		"question":"dea56c07f2",
		"answer":"dea56c07f2"
		
},
		{

		"quizItemId":3,
		"quizId":1,
		"question":"7fa121e925",
		"answer":"7fa121e925"
		
},
		{

		"quizItemId":4,
		"quizId":1,
		"question":"86a7545827",
		"answer":"86a7545827"
		
},
		{

		"quizItemId":5,
		"quizId":1,
		"question":"fefdde5c44",
		"answer":"fefdde5c44"
		
},
		{

		"quizItemId":6,
		"quizId":1,
		"question":"9c233934c5",
		"answer":"9c233934c5"
		
},
		{

		"quizItemId":7,
		"quizId":1,
		"question":"9b613fe4f6",
		"answer":"9b613fe4f6"
		
},
		{

		"quizItemId":8,
		"quizId":1,
		"question":"30e996d547",
		"answer":"30e996d547"
		
},
		{

		"quizItemId":9,
		"quizId":1,
		"question":"1762c11153",
		"answer":"1762c11153"
		
},
		{

		"quizItemId":10,
		"quizId":1,
		"question":"f10fccf0a8",
		"answer":"f10fccf0a8"
		
}
		],
	"name":"Terrible Test Quiz",
	"description":"Just a bunch of JSON, hastily scratched together...",
	"extraData":null

}


[
	{
	"id":"1",
	"type":"1",
	"quizItems":[{
		"question":"funk",
		"answers":"funk"
		},
		{
		"question":"woot",
		"answers":"woot"
		}],
	"name":"Test DB Quiz",
	"description":"Fresh from the database!",
	"options":"",
	"extraData":""
	},
	{
	"id":"2",
	"type":"2",
	"quizItems":[],
	"name":"test02",
	"description":"test02",
	"options":"",
	"extraData":""
	},
	{
	"id":"3",
	"type":"2",
	"quizItems":[],
	"name":"test03",
	"description":"test03",
	"options":"",
	"extraData":""
	}
]